Akhilesh Verma: 23+9999
Himanshu Chaurasiya: 10022
Pulkit Goyal: 10022
Ishitwa Agrawal: 10022
Arpit Rajput: 10022
Ayush Gwari: 10022
Harshit Shukla: 10022
Chirag Agrawal: 10022
Abhishek Yadav: 10022
Utkarsh Patel: 10022
Saksham Sharma: 10022
Shivani Singh: 10022
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: 10022
Jatin Gupta: 10022
Surbhi Saxena: 10022
Rishabh Shakya: 10022
Supriya Verma: 10022
Abishek: 10022
Rajat Mangat: 10022
Vipin Paswan: 10022
Danish Siddiqui: 10022
Manik Upadhyay: 10022
Anisha Singh: 10022
Rifa Fatima: 10022
Ayush Mohan: 10022
Eklavya Singh: 10022
Devansh Kumar: 10022
Abhinav Kannaujia: 10022
Shruti Jain: 10022
Pravisht Goel: 10022
Garvit: 10022
Rohit Tomar: 10022
Ayushi Goel: 10022
Aditi Maheshwari: 10022
Yash Jaiswal: 10022
Shubhang Verma: 10022
Harsh Kumar: 10022
Anany Srivastava: 10022
Dhaval Jain: 10022
Saatvik Rawat: 10022
Harshita Singhal: 10022
Devansh Kumar: 10022
Soni Kumari: 10022
Shristi Shukla: 10022
Jigyansh Varshney: 10022
Deepanshu Gupta: 10022
Ujjwal Singh: 1022
Ujjwal Singh: 10022
Ankit Mishra: 10022
Supriya Verma: 4G*8 bit
Rajat Mangat: 32 G bits
Ujjwal Singh: 32
Anany Srivastava: 2^33
Harshit Shukla: 2^35
Shruti Jain: 2³⁵
Harsh Kumar: 2^35
Ishitwa Agrawal: 2^35
Anany Srivastava: 2^35
Devansh Kumar: 2^35 bits
Garvit: 2^35
Soni Kumari: 2^35
Saksham Sharma: 2^35
Shristi Shukla: 2^35
Anisha Singh: 2^35
Chaman Kumar: 2'35
Vipin Paswan: 2^35
Supriya Verma: 2^35
Surbhi Saxena: 2^35
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: 2^35
Eklavya Singh: 2^35
Saatvik Rawat: 2^35
Abhishek Yadav: 2^35
Chirag Agrawal: 2^35
Mayank Arya: 2'35
Utkarsh Patel: 2'35
Shubhang Verma: 2³⁵
Pulkit Goyal: 2³⁵
Supriya Verma: Page
Harsh Kumar: Page
Devansh Kumar: Page
Shristi Shukla: Page
Arpit Rajput: Ipage
Garvit: Page
Jatin Gupta: Page
Chirag Agrawal: Page
Ishitwa Agrawal: page
Soni Kumari: Page
Shruti Jain: Page
Surbhi Saxena: Page
Anany Srivastava: Page
Pravisht Goel: Page
Rifa Fatima: Page
Rishabh Shakya: Page
Jigyansh Varshney: Page
Harshita Singhal: Page
Shubhang Verma: Page
Utkarsh Patel: Page
Anany Srivastava: Sir vo page table ki row ke baare mei baat kr rha hoo
Anany Srivastava: Usmei sir page frame ka address hoga ki page hoga??
Akhilesh Verma: cache vs MM
Akhilesh Verma: HDD(VM) vs MM
Harsh Kumar: Cache is faster and smaller than MM
MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Shristi Shukla: Cache is used to fasten the time and Virtual memory is used to increase the space for the operation
Abhinav Kannaujia: Cache is faster than MM. It consumes less access time as compared to MM.
Jatin Gupta: Cache is faster and smaller than MM
MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Chirag Agrawal: Cache is used to fasten the time and Virtual memory is used to increase the space for the operation if enough memory is not in MM
Harshit Shukla: Cache>mm>hdd
Raghvendra Pratap Singh: Cash memory is costier than main memory.Cache memory is smaller and faster memory
Chaman Kumar: Cache is used for faster the memory.. And it is more faster then mm
Ayush Gwari: Cache is faster than main memory and consumes less time, virtual memory is used to increase space .
Vipin Paswan: Cache is faster and smaller than MM
MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Abhinav Kannaujia: MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Mayank Arya: Cache is much faster and convinent than MMM
But MMM is more compact and faster than HDD
Soni Kumari: Cache memory is faster than main memory. It consumes less access time as compared to main memory.
MM is faster than and smaller than HDD
Ishitwa Agrawal: cache is used to store data temporarily for fast performance. while MMU is used for Virtual memory address translation.
Manik Upadhyay: Cache memory is a high speed memory that is used to store frequently accessed data. ... Main memory is also known as Random Access Memory (RAM). It is a memory unit that directly interacts with the CPU
Mohit Kumar Singh: Cache>MM>> HDD
Danish Siddiqui: Cache is faster than MM. It takes less access time as compared to Main memory
Preetika Jain: Cache is faster than MM but
MM is smaller than HDD nd take less time.
Ankit Mishra: Cache memory is the fastest memory
Rajat Mangat: Cache is faster and smaller than MM
MM is faster n smaller than HDD(VM). VM is allocated when operating system is installed.
Pulkit Agarwal: Cache memory is faster than main memory. It consumes less access time as compared to main memory. It stores the program that can be executed within a short period of time.
Abishek: Cache is faster , smaller than MM
MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Aditi Maheshwari: Cache is faster than MM and MM is faster than HDD
Saksham Sharma: Cache is faster and smaller than MM
MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Jigyansh Varshney: Cache helps us in reducing time as compared to MM and MM is much faster and smaller than HDD
Rashmee Pandey: Cache is faster as compared to MM
MM is faster as compared to HDD
Yash Jaiswal: MM is smaller and consumes more access time than cache . MM is faster and smaller than HDD
Arpit Rajput: Cache is a faster and smaller than MM and MM is faster nd smaller than hdd
Saatvik Rawat: Cache memory is faster than MM and smaller than MM
Anisha Singh: Cache is used to increase the speed and VM is used to increase the space.Cache is faster than MM.
Ayush Mohan: Cache is faster as compared to MM
MM is faster as compared to HDD
Shivani Singh: Chache memory is faster than MM.
It's take less access time than mm
Rohit Tomar: MM is faster and smaller than HDD
Cache is fast and smaller than mm
Rifa Fatima: Cache memory is used to increase speed amd is faster than mm
Main memory size is faster and smaller than hdd
Mohit Kumar Singh: Cache helps us in reducing time as compared to MM and MM is much faster and smaller than HDD
Shubhang Verma: Cache is faster than MM and MM is faster than HDD
Garvit: Read access on MM has to travel via memory bus while cache is much faster as it is right there
Also main memory is faster as well as smaller than HDD
Abhishek Yadav: Cache memory is faster than main memory. And Main memory is faster than VM
Harshita Singhal: Cache is fast than main memory and it takes less access time and main memory is faster than HDD
Pulkit Agarwal: Mm is faster than HDD
Supriya Verma: Cache is faster than main memory...it consume less time as comptto main memory
Pravisht Goel: Cache is very faster and smaller than main memory
Mm is faster than hdd
Utkarsh Patel: Cache memory is faster & cache memory increases the space for operations to perform
Anany Srivastava: Cache memory is faster than main memory. It consumes less access time as compared to main memory. MM is smaller than HDD
Shruti Jain: Cache is faster and smaller than mm and mm is faster and smaller than hdd
Cache>mm>hdd
Surbhi Saxena: Cache is faster than mm. However mm is better and faster than hdd
Rishabh Shakya: Cache memory is faster than main memory. It consumes less access time compared to main memory
Eklavya Singh: Cache is faster than MM
Mm is faster than HDD
Shikha Gupta: Cache is faster and smaller than MM ,MM is faster n smaller than HDD
Utkarsh Patel: Cache memory is faster & virtual memory increases the space for operations to perform
Pulkit Goyal: Cache is fast ,temporarily stored,and have less space compare to MM
MM is smaller than hdd ,mm is volatile but hdd is not volatile
Himanshu Chaurasiya: CM is about 5 to 10 times faster than MM.
HDD is permanent and MM is temporary.
Dhaval Jain: Cache is faster but smaller than MM
MM is used for virtual memory adress translation
Ujjwal Singh: Chace is smaller, faster and costlier than main memory
Devansh Kumar: Cache is faster than MM, requires less access time and is small in size than MM.
MM is smaller than HDD, requires less access time as co.pared to HDD
Cache > MM > HDD
Ujjwal Singh: Cache*
Ishitwa Agrawal: HDD(Virtual memory) is computer system memory space which can act as if it is a part of ram.
MMU is used for Virtual memory address translation.It used to allocate the address to be used as virtual memory.
Shivanshu Srivastava: Cache is usually faster than mm and mm is faster and smaller than hdd
Vikas Kumar Singh: Cache is usually faster than mm and mm is faster and smaller than hdd
Ayushi Goel: Cache is fast mm is slow